Guide to the Joint Western Area Committee Records, 1965-2004 LAC0003
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
Joint Western Area Committee records
1965-2004
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
LAC0003
65.75 Linear Feet 132 document boxes
The Joint Western Area Committee (JWAC) was one of four area conferences of the Teamsters, and served as a semi-autonomous intermediary organization between the local units of the IBT, and the national organization. The collection contains agendas, minutes, and proceedings from the Joint Western Area Committee (JWAC) of the Western Conference of Teamsters Freight Division for the period from 1965 until 2004.
Historical Note
The Joint Western Area Committee (JWAC) was one of four area conferences of the Teamsters, and served as a semi-autonomous intermediary organization between the local units of the IBT, and the national organization. The first Western conference of Teamsters was organized in 1937 under the leadership of Dave Beck, and united members from eleven Western states, including British Columbia. However, the conferences were not integrated into the administrative structure of the union until 1947. According to Sam Romer's study of the International Brotherhood of Teamsters (NY and London: John Wiley & Sons, 1962), the area conferences were self-contained, smaller replicas of the international union, and were comprised of all locals within its geographic boundaries. "The rise of the area conference marks the end of the local union in collective bargaining," Romer wrote (84). The area conferences were equally financed by the international union, and by affiliated locals. In 1994, Teamsters president Ron Carey dismantled the area conferences, including JWAC, as part of a larger re-organization of the union. The JWAC records reflect the broad responsibilities of the Western area conference, and document the complex process of enforcing the National Master Freight Agreement at the regional level. The summaries and transcripts of committee hearings highlight grievances and disputes in the freight business at the regional level, and also offer insights into the impact of de-regulation of the freight industry in the 1970s on individual workers.
Scope and Contents
The collection contains agendas, minutes, and proceedings from the Joint Western Area Committee (JWAC) of the Western Conference of Teamsters Freight Division for the period from 1965 until 2004. The JWAC records include an almost complete run of agendas and minutes of quarter-annually JWAC meetings from 1965-1996. The proceedings include summaries of cases discussed at the committee level, and many verbatim transcripts of committee hearings. JWAC committees and sub-committees (including the Main Committee, Change of Operations Committee, Over-The-Road Committee, Local Operations Committee, Joint Council # 7 Disputes, Break Bulk Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations & Suspensions/Warning Letters, California Trucking Association Committee) held hearings in grievance cases that could not be resolved at the local level. The committees evolved and varied over the time period documented in this collection. The hearings cover a wide range of grievances reflecting work conditions in the trucking business, for example disputes related to change of operations, violations of seniority privileges, grievances regarding payment, sick-leave, holidays, among many other issues. While all committee hearings are documented in the summaries that are included in the agendas and minutes of the meetings, not all committee hearings are transcribed in full. The existing transcripts are not arranged in the same consecutive numerical order as the summaries of the committee hearings for a particular meeting (for example, the transcript for the proceedings of a committee discussing case number 8-84-2232 may be found prior to the transcript of the case number 8-84-2227). Both transcripts, however, can be found in the collection of records from the JWAC meeting in August of 1984. Therefore, when searching for corresponding transcripts of committee hearings listed in the summaries, researchers should always consult the entire collection of transcripts of hearings held by a particular committee during a meeting. Proceedings for August and November 1969 are missing from the collection and there are no records for the period from 1996 to 2003.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection contains grievance records that contain the names of parties, grievants, and/or witnesses and using these will require the following procedure. All researchers using this collection will be asked to sign the User Statement Regulating Access document stating that he/she will not use the names of the parties, grievant or witnesses from the file in any publication, lecture or other venue.
Arrangement
Arranged chronologically.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Gift of IBT Local 70, Oakland, CA and the Labor Archives Research Center, San Francisco, 2009 (2011.042)
Trucking; Trucking -- Law and Legislation; Trucking -- United States; West (U.S.); Western Conference of Teamsters; International Brotherhood of Teamsters
- JWAC February 1965, 1965 February; LAC0003 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  Minutes, Agenda of Meeting, February 8-12, 1965; Change of Operations and Dispute Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1965 [1/2], 1965 May; LAC0003 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  Transcript of Main Committee, May 11, 1965, Minutes, May 10-14, 1965; Change of Operations And Dispute Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1965 [2/2], 1965 May; LAC0003 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  Agenda, Meeting May 1965; Change of Operations and Dispute Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC August 1965 [1/2], 1965 August; LAC0003 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  Minutes Meeting August 9-12, 1965; Change of Operations and Dispute Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC August 1965 [2/2], 1965 August; LAC0003 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  Agenda Meeting August 1965; Change of Operations and Dispute Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC November 1965, 1965 November; LAC0003 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  Minutes of Meeting November 8-12, 1965; Change of Operations and Dispute Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC February 1966 [1/2], 1966 February; LAC0003 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  Minutes of Meeting February 14-18, 1966; Change of Operations and Dispute Cases (Summaries); Transcripts/proceedings of Main Committee, February 15,1966
- JWAC February 1966 [2/2], 1966 February; LAC0003 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  Minutes of Meeting February 14-18, 1966; Change of Operations and Dispute Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1966, 1966 May; LAC0003 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  Agenda Meeting May 9-13, 1966, Change of Operations and Dispute Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC August 1966 [1/2], 1966 August; LAC0003 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  Transcript of Main Committee, August 9, 1966; Agenda Meeting August 8-12, 1966; Change of Operations and Dispute Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC August 1966 [2/2], 1966 August; LAC0003 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  Change of Operations and Dispute Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC November 1966 [1/2], 1966 November; LAC0003 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  Agenda, Meeting November 14-18, 1966, Change of Operations and Dispute Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC November 1966 [2/2], 1966 November; LAC0003 (Box 3, Folder 2)
- JWAC February 1967 [1/2], 1967 February; LAC0003 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  Minutes, Agenda of Meeting, February 13-17, 1967, Agenda; Change of Operations and Dispute Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC February 1967 [2/2], 1967 February; LAC0003 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- JWAC May 1967 [1/2], 1967 May; LAC0003 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  Change of Operations and Dispute Cases (summaries, filed in April 1967); Transcript/Proceedings of Specially-Appointed Committee, May 11, 1967, Dispute Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1967 [2/2], 1967 May; LAC0003 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  Agenda Meeting May 8-12, 1967; Change of Operations and Dispute Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC August 1967, 1967 August; LAC0003 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  Minutes of Meeting August 14-18, Change of Operations and Dispute Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC November 1967, 1967 November; LAC0003 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  Transcript Main Committee November 17, 1967;Minutes of Meeting, November 13-17, 1967, Change of Operations and Dispute Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC February 1968, 1968 February; LAC0003 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  Minutes of Meeting, San Francisco, February 12-16, 1968; Dispute Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1968 [1/2], 1968 May; LAC0003 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  Agenda; Dispute Cases
- JWAC May 1968 [2/2], 1968 May; LAC0003 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  Minutes of Meeting San Francisco May 6-10, 1968; Change of Operations and Dispute Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC August 1968 [1/2], 1968 August; LAC0003 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  Meeting August 12-16, 1968; Minutes, Agenda, Summaries
- JWAC August 1968 [2/2], 1968 August; LAC0003 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  Minutes; Agenda; Summaries; Transcript of Special JC#7 Committee, August 14, 1968
- JWAC November 1968 [1/2], 1968 November; LAC0003 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  Proceedings of the Special JC#7 Committee, November 12-13, 1968; Minutes Meeting November 11, 1968,
- JWAC November 1968 [2/2], 1968 November; LAC0003 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  Agenda Meeting November 11-15; Change of Operations and Dispute Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC February 1969 [1/2], 1969 February; LAC0003 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  Proceedings/transcript of Special JC#7 Committee, February 4-5, 1969; Agenda Meeting February 3-7, 1969; Dispute Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC February 1969 [2/2], 1969 February; LAC0003 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  Agenda Meeting February 3-7, 1969; Dispute Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1969 [1/2], 1969 May; LAC0003 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  Agenda Meeting May 13-16, 1969; Dispute Cases (Summaries); Proceedings of the Special JC#7 Committee
- JWAC May 1969 [2/2], 1969 May; LAC0003 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  Minutes of Meeting May 12-15, 1969; Dispute Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC February 1970, 1970 February; LAC0003 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  Agenda Meeting February 9-13, 1970; Change of Operations and Dispute Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1970, 1970 May; LAC0003 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  Proceedings of the Special Joint Council #7 Committee; Minutes and Agenda of Meeting May 11-15, 1970; Change of Operations and Dispute Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC August 1970 [1/4], 1970 August; LAC0003 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  Agenda Meeting August 10-14, 1970; Change of Operations and Dispute Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC August 1970 [2/4], 1970 August; LAC0003 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  Transcripts Change of Operations Committee, August 11, 1970; California Bay Area Labor Management Committee, August 18, 1970; Change of Operations Committee, August 12, 1970; Special Joint Council #7 Committee, August 11, 1970
- JWAC August 1970 [3/4], 1970 August; LAC0003 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  Transcripts Change of Operations Committee, August 11-13, 1970
- JWAC August 1970 [4/4], 1970 August; LAC0003 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  Transcripts Change of Operations Committee, August 13, 1970
- JWAC November 1970 [1/3], 1970 November; LAC0003 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  Agenda Meeting November 9-13, 1970; Change of Operations and Dispute Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC November 1970 [2/3], 1970 November; LAC0003 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  Minutes Meeting November 9-13, 1970; Change of Operations and Dispute Cases (Summaries); Proceedings/Transcripts of Special JC#7 Committee, November 11-12, 1970
- JWAC November 1970 [3/3], 1970 November; LAC0003 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  Transcripts Main Committee; Special JC#7 Committee, November 11, 1970
- JWAC February 1971 [1/2], 1971 February; LAC0003 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  Minutes of Meeting, February 8-12, 1971; Change of Operations and Dispute Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC February 1971 [2/2], 1971 February; LAC0003 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  Agenda; Change of Operations and Dispute Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1971 [1/2], 1971 May; LAC0003 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  Minutes of Meeting May 10-14, 1971; Transcript of Main and Change of Operations Committee; Change of Operations, Dispute Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1971 [2/2], 1971 May; LAC0003 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  Change of Operations, Dispute Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC August 1971 [1/2], 1971 August; LAC0003 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  Agenda Meeting August 9-13, 1971; Change of Operations, Dispute Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC August 1971 [2/2], 1971 August; LAC0003 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  Proceedings/Transcript of JC#7 Disputes, August 11, 1971; Minutes Meeting, August 9-13, 1971; Change of Operations, Dispute Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC November 1971 [1/2], 1971 November; LAC0003 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  Minutes of Meeting November 15-19, 1971; Change of Operations, Dispute Cases (Summaries); Proceedings of JC#7 Disputes and Committee for Local Operations, November 1971
- JWAC November 1971 [2/2], 1971 November; LAC0003 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  Agenda, Change of Operations, Dispute Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC February 1972 [1/3], 1972 February; LAC0003 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  Transcripts, Committee for Local Operations, February 1972
- JWAC February 1972 [2/3], 1972 February; LAC0003 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  Transcripts, Committee for Local Operations, February 1972; Minutes Meeting, February 14-18, 1972; Change of Operations, Dispute Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC February 1972 [3/3], 1972 February; LAC0003 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  Agenda Meeting February 14-18, 1972; Change of Operations, Dispute Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1972 [1/2], 1972 May; LAC0003 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  Proceedings/Transcripts, Main Committee, Committee for Local Operations
- JWAC May 1972 [2/2], 1972 May; LAC0003 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  Minutes of Meeting, May 8-12, 1972; Change of Operations, Dispute Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC August 1972 [1/3], 1972 August; LAC0003 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  Transcripts/Proceedings Change of Operations and Main Committees
- JWAC August 1972 [2/3], 1972 August; LAC0003 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  Minutes of Meeting, August 14-18, 1972; Change of Operations, Dispute Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC August 1972 [3/3], 1972 August; LAC0003 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  Agenda, August 14-18, 1972; Change of Operations, Dispute Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC November 1972 [1/3], 1972 November; LAC0003 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  Agenda Meeting November 6-10, 1972; Change of Operations, Dispute Cases (Summaries), Transcripts Change of Operations Committee
- JWAC November 1972 [2/3], 1972 November; LAC0003 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  Transcripts Change of Operations Committee
- JWAC November 1972 [3/3], 1972 November; LAC0003 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  Transcripts Committee for Local Operations, JC#7 Cases, November 1972; Change of Operations, Dispute Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1973, 1973 May; LAC0003 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  Transcripts/Proceedings, Committee for Local Operations, May 18, 1973
- JWAC February 1974 [1/2], 1974 February; LAC0003 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  Minutes Meeting, February 11-15, 1974; Change of Operations, Dispute Cases (Summaries); Transcripts Change of Operations Committee, Main Committee, JC# 7 Cases
- JWAC February 1974 [2/2], 1974 February; LAC0003 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  Agenda of Meeting, February 11-15, 1974; Committee for Local Operations Cases, JC#7 Disputes (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1974 [1/3], 1974 May; LAC0003 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  Minutes of Meeting, May 13-17, 1974; Change of Operations, Dispute Cases (Summaries); Transcripts Change of Operations Committee
- JWAC May 1974 [2/3], 1974 May; LAC0003 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  Proceedings/Transcripts of JC#7 Cases; Change of Operations, Main Committees, May 1974
- JWAC May 1974 [3/3], 1974 May; LAC0003 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  Agenda Meeting May 13-17, 1974; Change of Operations, Dispute Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC August 1974 [1/3], 1974 August; LAC0003 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  Agenda Meeting, August 12-16, 1974; Change of Operations, Dispute Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC August 1974 [2/3], 1974 August; LAC0003 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  Minutes Meeting, August 12-16, 1974; Change of Operations, Dispute Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC August 1974 [3/3], 1974 August; LAC0003 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  Proceedings of the Committee for Local Operations on JC#7 Cases, Change of Operations Committee
- JWAC November 1974 [1/4], 1974 February; LAC0003 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  Proceedings/Transcripts Main Committee, Change of Cperations Committee
- JWAC November 1974 [2/4], 1974 February; LAC0003 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  Minutes; Proceedings/Transcripts of the Committee for Local Operations, Change of Operations Committee
- JWAC November 1974 [3/4], 1974 February; LAC0003 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  Agenda Meeting November 11-15, 1974;Change of Operations, Dispute Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC November 1974 [4/4], 1974 February; LAC0003 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  Minutes of Meeting November 11-15, 1974; Change of Operations, Dispute Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC February 1975 [1/5], 1975 February; LAC0003 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  Minutes of Meeting February 10-14, 1975, Change of Operations, Dispute Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC February 1975 [2/5], 1975 February; LAC0003 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  Agenda; Change of Operations, Dispute Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC February 1975 [3/5], 1975 February; LAC0003 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  Transcripts/Proceedings Change of Operations Committee, Committee for Local Operations of Joint Council #7
- JWAC February 1975 [4/5], 1975 February; LAC0003 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  Agenda Meeting February 10-14, 1975; Change of Operations Committee and Dispute Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC February 1975 [5/5], 1975 February; LAC0003 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  Dispute Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1975 [1/5], 1975 May; LAC0003 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  Agenda May 12-16, 1975, Change of Operations Committee and Dispute Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1975 [2/5], 1975 May; LAC0003 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- JWAC May 1975 [3/5], 1975 May; LAC0003 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  Minutes of Meeting, May 12-16, 1975; Change of Operations and Dispute Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1975 [4/5], 1975 May; LAC0003 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  Change of Operations Committee (Summaries), Transcripts Change of Operations Committee/Main Committee
- JWAC May 1975 [5/5], 1975 May; LAC0003 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  Proceedings/Transcripts of Committee for Local Operations of JC#7, Change of Operations Committee
- JWAC August 1975 [1/4], 1975 August; LAC0003 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  Minutes; Proceedings/Transcripts Local Operations Committee, Change of Operations Committee
- JWAC August 1975 [2/4], 1975 August; LAC0003 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  Local Operations Committee, Main Committee, Dispute Cases, Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC August 1975 [3/4], 1975 August; LAC0003 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  Minutes of Meeting August 12-16, 1975; Change of Operations, Local Operations, Main Committees, Dispute Cases, Discharges. Terminations and Suspensions, Warning Letters (Summaries); Transcript Change of Operations Committee
- JWAC August 1975 [4/4], 1975 August; LAC0003 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  Proceedings/Transcripts Committee for Local Operations of JC#7, Change of Operations Committee
- JWAC November 1975 [1/4], 1975 November; LAC0003 (Box 17, Folder 2)
  Agenda, Minutes, Meeting November 3-7, 1975; Change of Operations, Local Operations of JC#7, Main Committees (Summaries)
- JWAC November 1975 [2/4], 1975 November; LAC0003 (Box 17, Folder 3)
  Transcripts/Proceedings of JC#7 Cases, Change of Operations Committee
- JWAC November 1975 [3/4], 1975 November; LAC0003 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  Agenda Meeting November 3-7, 1975; Change of Operations, Local Operations of Joint Council #7, OTR Disputes Committees (Summaries)
- JWAC November 1975 [4/4], 1975 November; LAC0003 (Box 17, Folder 5)
  Disputes, Discharges. Terminations and Suspensions, Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC February 1976 [1/3], 1976 February; LAC0003 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  Transcripts/Proceedings, Change of Operations Committee, Transcripts of Meeting of Union Members of the JWAC and Representatives of Local Unions, February 1976
- JWAC February 1976 [2/3], 1976 February; LAC0003 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  Agenda Meeting February 9-13, 1976, Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council #7 Disputes, OTR and Master Disputes, Discharges, Terminations, Suspensions, Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC February 1976 [3/3], 1976 February; LAC0003 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  Minutes Meeting, Committee for Local Operations, Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council #7 Disputes (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1976 [1/5], 1976 May; LAC0003 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  Partial Proceedings of the Change of Operations Committee, Local Operations Committee
- JWAC May 1976 [2/5], 1976 May; LAC0003 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  Change of Operations Committee, Discharges, Terminations, Suspensions, Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1976 [3/5], 1976 May; LAC0003 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  Partial Proceedings of the Change of Operations Committee; Change of Operations Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1976 [4/5], 1976 May; LAC0003 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  Agenda Meeting May 10-14, 1976, Change of Operations, Multi-Conference, Jt. Council # 7 Disputes, P&D Disputes, Office Disputes Committees (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1976 [5/5], 1976 May; LAC0003 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  Main Committee, Discharges, Terminations, Suspensions, Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC Rules of Procedure, 1976 May; LAC0003 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  JWAC Rules of Procedure, rev 03/1976
- JWAC August 1976 [1/4], 1976 August; LAC0003 (Box 19, Folder 1)
  Minutes of Meeting August 9-13, 1976; Multi-Conference and Change of Operations Committee, Main Committee (Summaries)
- JWAC August 1976 [2/4], 1976 August; LAC0003 (Box 19, Folder 2)
  Transcript/Proceedings Change of Operations Committee
- JWAC August 1976 [3/4], 1976 August; LAC0003 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  Agenda Meeting August 9-13; Multi Conference and Change of operations Committees, Committee for Local Operations, Jt. Council #7 Disputes, Main Committee (Summaries)
- JWAC August 1976 [4/4], 1976 August; LAC0003 (Box 19, Folder 4)
  Main Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations, Suspensions, Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC October 1976, 1976 October; LAC0003 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  Change of Operations Cases
- JWAC November 1976 [1/4], 1976 November; LAC0003 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  Transcript of Meeting of the Union Members of the JWAC and Representatives of Local Unions, November 8, 1976; Minutes of Meeting November 8-12, 1976, Multi-Conference and Change of Operations, Main Committee (Summaries)
- JWAC November 1976 [2/4], 1976 November; LAC0003 (Box 19, Folder 7)
  Multi-Conference and Change of Operations Committee, Main Committee (Summaries)
- JWAC November 1976 [3/4], 1976 November; LAC0003 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  Committee for Discharges, Terminations, Suspensions, Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC November 1976 [4/4], 1976 November; LAC0003 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  Partial Transcript of Proceedings of the Change of Operations Committee; Change of Operations Cases (Summaries)
- JWAC February 1977 [1/2], 1977 February; LAC0003 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  Transcript of Proceedings of the Change of Operations Committee; Minutes of Meeting of Members of the JWAC and Representatives of Local Unions, February 14, 1977; Partial Proceedings of Local Operations Committee and of the Main Committee
- JWAC February 1977 [2/2], 1977 February; LAC0003 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  Agenda, Meeting February 14-18, 1977; Multi-Conference and Change of Operations, Main Committee, Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes, Discharges, Terminations, Suspensions, Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1977 [1/4], 1977 May; LAC0003 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  Proceedings/Transcripts of the Committee for Local Operations, Main Committee
- JWAC May 1977 [2/4], 1977 May; LAC0003 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  Minutes of Meeting May 9-13, 1977; Multi-Conference and Change of Operations, Main Committee, Committee for Discharges, Terminations, Suspensions, Warning Letters (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1977 [3/4], 1977 May; LAC0003 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  Agenda; Multi-Conference and Change of Operations, Committee for Local Operations, Joint Council # 7 Disputes (Summaries)
- JWAC May 1977 [4/4], 1977 May; LAC0003 (Box 21, Folder 1)